Hey, Eddie.
에디?
-What are you doing here?
-Watching you sleep.
- 여기서 뭐 하고 있어?
- 그냥 자는 거 보고 있었어
Why?
왜?
It makes me feel peaceful.
그럼 마음이 편해지거든
어서 자
Please.
I can't sleep now!
나보고 지금 잠을 자라고
You want me to sing?
자장가 불러 줄까?
됐어, 이젠 끝이야
당장 이 집에서 나가 줘
That's it. I want you
out of the apartment now!
그게 무슨 소리야?
What are you talking about?
Hannibal Lecter?
'양들의 침묵' 알지?
Better roommate than you.
그 박사랑 사는 게 낫겠다
I don't think you're being fair! One
night you see me and you get scared.
이건 불공평해, 딱 한 번
보고는 이렇게 기겁이라니
What about the other nights
when you don't see me?
네가 눈치 못 챘던 날이
얼마나 많은 줄 알아?
Last night you went
and got some water...
어젯밤엔 네가 일어나서
물 마시러 나가길래
난 문 뒤로 숨었다고
...and I was nice enough
to hide behind the door.
I didn't realize that.
그런 줄 몰랐어
Get out now!
당장 나가!
정말 나가길 바래?
You really want me out?
Yes, please.
제발 부탁이야
Then I want to hear you say
you want me out.
좋아, 정확하게 듣고 싶어
나가 달라고 말해 봐
I want you out.
- 나가 줘!
- 아니, 입술로 말해
I want to hear it from your lips.
Where'd you hear it before?
언제는 내가 발로 말했냐?
All right. You know what?
Consider me gone.
알았어, 내가 나갔다고 생각해
I'll be out by the time
you get home from work tomorrow.
내일 네가 퇴근할 때쯤
다시 돌아올게
-Thank you.
-I heard that.
- '고맙다'
- 다 들었어
The One Where Eddie Won't Go
- 나 왔어
- 어서 와
Well, look at you!
아니, 너...
Finally got that
time machine working, huh?
드디어 그 고리짝 물건을
구했구나
You like it?
좋아? 8번가에서 팔고 있더라
This guy was selling them
on 8th Avenue and I thought...
이걸 보고 생각했지
내게 부족한 게 뭘까?
... "You know what I don't have?"
A mirror?
거울?
Fine, make fun.
I think it's jaunty.
그래, 실컷 웃어라
네 쾌활함이 날 채워 줘
For a guy who's recently lost his job,
you're in a good mood.
실업자 치곤 꽤 긍정적이구나
그럼, 난 걱정 없어
바닥에서 시작하는 게 아냐
I'll be all right.
I'm not starting from square one.
I was Dr. Drake Ramoray
on Days of our Lives.
이래봬도
라모레 박사님이었다구
That's got to have some kind of cachet.
최소한의 기득권은
확보한 셈이지
Cachet? Jaunty?
어려운 단어만 쓰네
Chandler gave me
word-of-the-day toilet paper.
챈들러가 '어휘력 도우미'
휴지를 줬거든
커피 좀 마셔야겠다
I'm gonna get some coffee.
- 안녕
- 왔어?
너, 너!
그 책 읽었니?
So? Did you read the book?
그 책...
엄청나더라
Oh, my God.
It was incredible!
- 완전히 네 얘기지?
- 무슨 책인데 그래?
Didn't it, like,
totally speak to you?
What book is this?
You have to read this book.
It's called Be Your Own Wind Keeper.
레이첼, 너도 읽어 봐야 돼
'바람은 스스로 지켜라'인데
여자가 힘을 갖는 게
얼마나 중요한지 나와
It's about how women need
to become more empowered.
그리고 바람이 나와
But there's wind.
바람이 우리를 여신으로
만들어 준대
And the wind can make us goddesses.
Do you know who takes our wind?
Men. They just take it.
바람을 누가 빼앗는지 아니?
남자야, 그들이 가져갔어
Men just take our wind?
남자가 우리 바람을 빼앗아가?
맞아, 늘 그랬어
그들은 무기 소지자거든
All the time. Because they
are the lightning-bearers.
멋진 말이다
난쟁이 호빗 얘기 같은데
That sounds kind of cool.
It's like The Hobbit.
It is nothing like The Hobbit.
호빗과는 전혀 상관없어
It's like reading about
every relationship I've ever had.
내 얘기가 그대로 쓰여진
느낌이야, 리차드는 빼고
Except for Richard.
물론이지, 그는 네 바람을
빼앗을 사람이 아냐
Richard would never steal your wind.
- 먹기 딱 좋은 남자잖니?
- 그래
Because he's yummy.
But all the others.
- 다른 남자들은 못 믿어
- 맞아
And the part about how
they're always drinking...
또 있어, 남자들은 여자의
잠재력을 마구 짓밟지만
...from our pool of inner power.
But God forbid we should take a sip.
여자는 남자 것을
손도 못 대게 돼 있어
Anybody want a cruller?
꽈배기 먹을 사람?
저게 무기의 전형적인 형태야
This is a typical
lightning-bearer thing.
마치 이러는 것 같잖아
It's like...
누구 내 물건처럼 생긴
꽈배기 먹을 사람?
... "Hello. Who wants one of
my phallic-shaped man-cakes?"
Don't worry about it, already!
Things happen.
겁먹지 마
흔한 일이라고
내가 잘린 게 화 안 나세요?
You're not mad at me
for getting fired and everything?
조이, 날 봐
Look at me.
Look at me!
나를 쳐다보라니까!
Do I have lipstick on my teeth?
내 이빨에 립스틱 묻었어?
아뇨
재기할 수 있을까요?
Can we get back to me?
이봐, 이 바닥은
오늘 내일을 장담 못해
Look, honey. People get fired
left and right in this business.
I already got you an audition
for Another World.
내가 벌써 널 '또 다른 세상'
오디션에 끼워 넣었어
고마워요
All right!
"Cab Driver Number 2"?
택시운전사 2번요?
고맙지?
You're welcome.
But I was Dr. Drake Ramoray!
전 라모레 박사였다구요
How can I go from being
a neurosurgeon to driving a cab?
신경외과 전문의가 어떻게
택시 같은 걸 운전해요?
Things change. Roll with them.
상황이 바뀌면
대처할 줄도 알아야지
겨우 두 줄뿐이잖아요
But this is a two-line part!
It's like taking a step backwards.
이건 완전히 퇴보예요
I'm not gonna do this.
전 못해요
조이!
알 민자와 그 패거리한테도
경고했지만 다시 말하지
I'm gonna tell you the same thing
I told Al Minza...
...and his pyramid of dogs.
Take any job you can get,
and don't make on the floor.
가리는 거 없이 받아먹어
혼자 잘난 척 말고
안 되겠어요, 다음에 오죠
I'm sorry.
I'll see you.
세상에!
이건 완전히...
God!
Oh, God!
I mean, it's just so....
그렇지?
Isn't it?
내 얘기를 책으로 읽는 것 같아
This is like reading
about my own life!
This book could have been called
Be Your Own Wind Keeper, Rachel!
제목을 이렇게 해도 되겠어
'바람은 스스로 지켜라, 레이첼'
It wouldn't have sold
a million copies...
베스트셀러는 아니지만
너한테는 좋은 선물이
됐을 거야
...but it would've made
a nice gift for you.
- 안녕, 얘들아
- 안녕?
Sweetie, we've got to go.
자기, 이제 가야지
싫어!
싫다니?
내가 왜 항상 네 시간표에
맞춰 움직여야 하지?
No! Why do we always have to do
everything according to your timetable?
Actually, it's the movie theater
that has the timetable.
시간표는 극장에서 정한 거야
그래야 첫 장면 놓치지 않지
It's so you don't miss the beginning.
This isn't about the movie theater.
This is about you stealing my wind.
극장 얘기가 아냐
내 바람을 훔쳐간 네 얘기라구
파이팅, 레이첼!
You go, girl!
I can't pull that off, can l?
내가 하니까 영 이상하지?
잠깐만, 네 바람이라고?
Excuse me, your wind?
그래, 내 바람
Yes, my wind.
How do you expect me to grow
if you won't let me blow?
네가 날 위에서 눌러 대니
내가 숨이나 쉴 수 있겠어?
난... 그 정도는...
You know I don't...
... have a problem with that.
아니었어
좋아
I just really need to be
with myself right now.
난 이제부터
내 의지대로 행동할 거야
I'm sorry.
미안해
그렇지, 사과할 필요도 없어
You're right.
I don't have to apologize.
미안해, 내가 미쳐!
Sorry. Damn it!
내용이 뭐야?
-What is it?
-I don't know.
나도 몰라, 바람, 나무
연못에 관한 얘기라는데
It's got all this stuff
about wind and trees...
...and some sacred pool.
I don't really get it.
But she's pretty upset about it.
뭔지 모르지만
레이첼이 아주 열받아 있어
내가 책 좋아하는 여자들하고
달리 데이트를 안 하겠니?
This is why I don't date
women who read.
What's that?
왜? 뭔데 그래?
It's my VlSA bill.
신용카드 결제 청구서야
첫 번째 통고래
Envelope one of two.
- 좋은 내용일 리 없어
- 열어 봐
-That can't be good.
-Open it, open it.
세상에!
Oh, my God!
이거 봐
언제 이걸 다 썼지?
Look at this!
How did I spend so much money?
조이, 그건 수수료야
이게 전체 금액이라고
That's just the minimum amount.
That's your total.
'도자기 수렵여행'에서
3천 5백 달러?
Thirty-five hundred dollars
at "Porcelain Safari"?
동물들 산 곳이야
My animals.
내 품위에 맞댔어
사투리를 알아들을 수 있어야지
The guy said they suited me. He spoke
with an accent. I was confused.
I don't know what to do!
이제 어쩌지?
'또 다른 세상'에서
택시운전사 해야지 뭐
You can start by driving a cab
on Another World.
- 뭐?
- 오디션 말야
-What?
-That audition?
That's a two-line part!
겨우 두 줄짜리야
'사랑해요, 투명유리'에선
천 백 달러나 썼어
Joey, you owe $1100
at "I Love Lucite."
-So what?
-So suck it up, man.
- 그래서?
- 그거 해, 돈 벌어야지
It's a job. It's money.
성인군자처럼 현학적으로
조언해 대지 마
I don't need you getting judgmental
and condescending and pedantic.
Toilet paper?
- 화장지에서 배운 거야?
- 그래
잘난체가 아냐
이건 현실 얘기라구
I'm not being any of those things.
I'm being realistic.
- 그만둬, 내 친구 맞니?
- 난 네 친구야
You're supposed to be my friend!
I am your friend.
그럼 이래야지
Then tell me things like,
"You'll be fine."
'걱정 마, 친구, 끝까지 버텨
좋은 일이 생길 거야'
And "Something big's gonna
come along. I know it!"
난 그런 거 몰라
But I don't know it.
내가 아는 건 네가 다른 데서도
2,300달러나 썼다는 거야
What I do know is you owe $2300
at "lsn't It Chromantic?"
I'm aware of what I owe.
내가 많이 썼다는 건 알아
생각해 봐, 그 일자리
구하는 데 10년이나 걸렸어
Then get some sense.
It took you 10 years to get that job.
또 구하려면 얼마나 걸리겠어?
-How long till you get another?
-I don't want to hear this!
듣고 싶지 않아
I'm just saying....
- 내 말은...
- 됐어, 그만 해!
Well, don't "just say"!
- 난 갈래
- 그래
Maybe I should just go.
그래, 다음에 봐
I'll see you later.
Just think about it.
하지만 잘 생각해 봐
I don't need to think about it!
생각할 것도 없어
I was Dr. Drake Ramoray!
난 라모레 박사였다구!
That was huge!
주연급이었어!
Big things are gonna happen!
You'll see!
멋진 일이 일어날 거야
두고 보라구, 로스!
Ross!
You still there?
아직 거기 있어?
안녕, 친구?
What are you still doing here?
에디, 아직도 안 간 거야?
과일과 야채를 탈수시키는데
진짜 환상적이야!
Just some basic dehydrating
of fruits and vegetables.
Man alive, this thing's fantastic!
Aren't you forgetting anything?
에디, 뭐 잊은 거 없어?
있지, 새 금붕어를 샀어
Oh, yeah. I got us a new goldfish.
저번 것보다 더 쌩쌩해
He's feistier than the last one.
후추를 뿌렸는데
어떤 놈이 살아 남냐?
Maybe because the last one
was made by Pepperidge Farm.
Eddie, isn't there something
you're supposed to be doing now?
그거 말고 당장 할 일이 있잖아?
탈수시키는 거 말고는 없어
나 지금 탈수에 미쳐 있거든!
Not unless it's got something
to do with dehydrating.
Because right now,
I'm a dehydrating maniac!
이미 얘기 끝났잖아
지금쯤 넌...
I thought we had a deal.
I thought by the time I got
이게 뭔지 알아?
You know what that is?
Your last roommate's kidney?
네 전 룸메이트의 신장?
아니, 이건 토마토야
That's a tomato.
전시해도 될 정도지?
This one definitely goes
in the display.
Hey, Gunther.
Let me get a lemonade to go.
건터, 레모네이드 하나
포장해 줘
레모네이드라...
괜찮아?
Lemonade?
You okay, man?
It's career stuff.
일이 안 풀려
드라마에서 날 죽였어
They killed off
my character on the show.
That's too bad.
How'd they do it?
안됐군, 어떻게?
엘리베이터 통로로 떨어졌지
I fell down an elevator shaft.
심하군, 난 눈사태로 죽었어
That sucks.
I was buried in an avalanche.
What?
- 뭐?
- 나도 배우였어
I used to be Brice
on All My Children.
Why must everybody watch me sleep?
왜들 내가 자는 걸 쳐다보지?
There'll be no more
watching me sleep! No more...
더 이상 쳐다보지 마
...watching!
- 난 그냥...
- 시끄러워!
I got some great stuff to dehydrate.
Grapes, apricots.
탈수시킬 좋은 재료를 찾았어
포도, 살구...
물풍선을 탈수시키면
어떻게 될까?
I thought it'd be cool to see
what happens with these water balloons.
Get out.
Get out, get out, get out!
나가!
나가, 나가, 나가라구!
-What?
-You! Move out!
- 뭐?
- 너 말야, 당장 나가!
Take your fruit!
Your stupid small fruit and get out!
이 거지 같은 쬐그만
과일들 가지고 당장 나가!
정말 내가 나가길 바래?
You want me to move out?
저 말이지...
너무 느닷없는 거 아냐?
I gotta tell you, that's kind of
out of the blue, don't you think?
느닷없다구?
This is not out of the blue!
This is smack-dab
in the middle of the blue!
넌 나한테 날벼락이었어!
진정해, 너무 그러지 마
Relax! Take it easy, buddy!
You don't have to tell me twice.
두 번씩 말할 필요 없어
짐꾼을 불러야겠군
Someone will be by for my stuff.
내 물고기를 놔두고 갈 거라고
생각했다면 넌 미친놈이야!
If you think I'm leaving you
alone with my fish, you're insane!
- 도와 줄까?
- 필요 없어, 냉정한 놈
You want some help?
No help required, chico!
All the way to the airport, huh?
You know, that's over 30 miles.
'공항에 가는 길요?'
'48km가 넘으니까
꽤 줘야 할 거요'
That's gonna cost you about so bucks.
50달러라고 써 있잖아
Excuse me, that's fifty bucks.
- 네?
- 50달러!
Five-O dollars.
You know what it is?
It's smudgy because they're fax pages.
팩스로 온 거라서
확실히 안 보여요
When I was on Days of our Lives
as Dr. Drake Ramoray...
'우리들의 삶'에서
라모레 박사 역을 했을 땐
프린트된 진짜 대본을
집까지 보내 줬죠
...they'd send over
the whole script on real paper.
That's great.
좋았겠군
장면을 늘이면 어때요?
If you wanted to expand this scene,
like have the cab crash...
사고가 나서 내가
피해자들을 돌보는 거예요
... I could attend to the victims...
... because I have a background
in medical acting.
전에는 의사였다구요
Okay, listen, thanks for coming in.
됐어, 와 줘서 고맙네
일어서지 마세요
최소한 끝까지 봐야죠
Don't thank me for coming in.
At least let me finish.
We could take the expressway...
'고속도로를 타도 되지만
이 시간엔 공항이 낫겠어요'
... but this time of day
you're better off taking the budge.
You were going for bridge there,
weren't you?
대본에는 '다리'로 돼 있죠?
잘 갈게요
I'll have a good day.
좋아, 질문 28번
Question number 28.
"Have you ever allowed
a lightning-bearer to take your wind?"
무기소지자가 당신의 바람을
가져가도록 허락한 적이 있나?
I would have to say no.
난 '없다'야
And I would have to say....
그럼 난 '웃긴다'라고 할게
What?
- 왜?
- 로봇 좋아하던 애 생각 안 나?
Do you not remember the puppet guy?
걔는 네 잠재력 연못에서
발씻은 거나 다름없어
You totally let him wash his feet
in the pool of your inner power.
그 로봇까지도 말야!
And his puppet too!
Well, at least
I didn't let some guy...
좋아, 난 적어도 첫 데이트에서
내 진실의 숲을 더럽히진 않았어
...into the forest of my righteous
truth on the first date!
-Who?
-Paul!
- 누구 말야?
- 폴
좋아, 다음 질문으로 넘어가자
Moving on, moving on.
Next question.
29번, 무기 소지자 때문에
다른 여신을 배신한 적이 있나?
Okay, number 29.
"Have you ever betrayed
another goddess...
...for a lightning-bearer?"
Okay, number 30.
통과, 30번!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Let's go back to 29.
29번 안 끝났어
내 기억으론 없어
Not to my recollection.
좋아, 중학교 때
데니 아색 기억 안 나?
Danny Arshack, ninth grade.
You know the bottle
was pointing at me.
걔가 완전히 나한테
빠져 있던 거 몰랐어?
Only because you took up
half the circle!
그렇게 꼬리를 쳐대니 당연하지
Listen to you two.
It's so sad.
너희 얘기 듣고 있으니
너무 마음 아프다
Looks like I'll be going to
the goddess meetings alone.
여신들 모임엔 나 혼자
가는 수밖에!
제이슨이 모니카랑 찢어진 지
한 시간밖에 안 됐을 때
Not when they find out
you slept with Jason Hurley...
...an hour after
he broke up with Monica.
네가 걔랑 잤다는 걸
모임에서 알면 큰일날걸
한 시간이라구?
One hour?
이 떠버리같으니!
You are such a leaf blower!
Be careful with that 3-D Last Supper.
Judas is a little loose.
'최후의 만찬'은 잘 다뤄요
유다가 좀 건들건들하거든요
Oh, my God! What's going on?
세상에, 무슨 일이야?
They're taking all my stuff back.
I guess you were right.
내 귀염둥이들을 반품했어
네 말이 맞았어
아니, 내가 틀렸다는 걸
말해 주려고 왔어
No, I wasn't right.
That's what I came here to tell you.
I was totally hung up
on my own stuff the other day.
그 때 내가 초라해 보여서
괜한 말을 지껄였어
난 늘 앞일을 걱정하면서
살아야 했다고
No, listen. I need the whole
security thing, you know?
카드 값을 미리 준비하고
넌 그럴 필요 없잖아
To know where my next paycheck is
coming from. But you don't need that.
And that's amazing to me.
그건 대단한 거야
I could never do what you do.
네가 부러워, 조이
-Thanks.
-You hold out for something bigger.
- 고마워, 로스
- 앞을 내다봐
그까짓 택시운전사 오디션에
안 간 네가 너무 자랑스러워
I can't tell you
how much respect I have...
...for you not going
to that stupid audition.
-I went.
-Great! How did it go?
- 갔었어
- 잘했다, 어땠어?
- 떨어졌어
- 잘됐다!
-I didn't get it.
-Good for you!
- 뭐?
- 넌 꿈이 있잖아
You're living the dream!
All right, then!
뭘 했든 잘했어
- 앵무새는 안 돼!
- 뭐?
Not my parrot.
I can't watch this.
차마 눈 뜨고 못 보겠어
Hey, hold on, hold on.
잠깐만요
How much for the....
How much to save the bird?
그 앵무새 얼마죠?
-Twelve hundred.
-Dollars?
- 천 2백이요
- 달러로요?
You spent $1200 on a plastic bird?
이 플라스틱 새한테
천 2백을 썼어?
충동구매였어
계산대 옆에 있었거든
It was an impulse buy.
Near the register.
됐으니까 가져가요
Go ahead with the bird.
2백 달러 선에서 없나요?
Do you have anything for around $200?
The dog.
저 개요
I'll take it.
내가 사겠어요
My gift to you, man.
내가 주는 선물이야
고마워, 로스
Thanks, Ross!
I really liked that bird, though.
난 그 새가 정말 좋은데
- 개도 좋아
- 그래
But the dog!
Here are your cakes.
케이크야
We didn't order cake.
주문한 적 없어
알아, 내가 내는 거야
No, I know. They're from me.
You guys, this is not good.
우리 이러지 말자
서로 이러지 않아도
남자들한테 충분히 고통받잖아
We have enough trouble
with guys stealing our wind...
...without taking it from each other.
You're right.
- 그래
- 알지?
I love you goddesses.
- 사랑해, 여신들아
- 나도 사랑해
다신 네 바람을 빼앗지 않을게
I don't ever want
to suck your wind again.
- 고마워, 이제 된 거지?
- 그래
-Thank you. So are we good?
-We're good.
We're good?
Let me take these back.
They'll take it out of my paycheck.
그럼 이 케이크 갖다놓을게
분명 내 월급에서 제할 거야
Ding-dong, the psycho's gone!
딩동, 사이코는 갔습니다
- 이번엔 확실해?
- 그럼, 직접 내 눈으로 봤어
Are you sure this time?
I actually saw him leave.
녀석이... 사람 머리를 들고
창문에 서 있네
That guy is holding a human head.
He's holding a human head!
창문에 서 있어!
Check it out, man!
이것 봐, 메이시스 백화점
뒷골목에서 베 왔어
I tore it off a mannequin
in the alley behind Macy's.
거긴 뒷골목이 없어
There's no alley behind Macy's.
So I got it in the junior miss
department. Big diff.
주니어 미스 백화점에서
얻었다, 왜?
이거면 다음 칵테일 파티 때
화재거리가 될 거야
It'll make a hell of a conversation
piece at our next cocktail party.
"Our next cocktail party"?
다음 칵테일 파티?
그래, 이 안에 먹을 걸 넣자
초콜릿 같은 거
We'll put chips in it.
We'll make it a chip chick.
Do you remember yesterday?
에디, 어제 일 생각나?
그럼, 어렴풋이 기억나
Yes, I think I vaguely recall it.
Do you remember
talking to me yesterday?
어제 네가 한 말은 기억나?
그럼
무슨 일이 있었지?
So what happened?
함께 라스베가스까지
드라이브했잖아?
We took a road trip to Las Vegas!
Oh, sweet Moses!
옴마야, 세상에나!
너희들 거기서 돈 좀 땄니?
So on this road trip,
did you win any money?
난 다 털렸어
하지만 이 포커 왕께서 다 땄지
I crapped out. But Mr. 21 here!
He cleans up!
$300! He buys me these new shoes.
신발도 이 친구가 사 줬어
멋지지?
Nice.
- 근사하다
- 위에서 봐, 안녕
See you upstairs. See you, pals!
Is anyone else starting
to really like him?
나 말고 또 쟤가 좋아진 사람?
이런...
뭐야?
도와 드릴까요?
May I help you?
내 열쇠가 왜 안 맞지?
내 물건은 왜 밖에 있어?
Why doesn't my key work,
and what's my stuff doing downstairs?
죄송합니다
I'm sorry.
우리가 아는 사이였던가요?
Have we met?
It's Eddie, you freak!
Your roommate.
난 에디야, 네 짝꿍
미안하지만...
I'm sorry...
... I already have a roommate.
제 짝꿍은 따로 있는데요
안녕하세요?
이 친구랑 산 지 몇 년 됐죠
무슨 말씀이신지 모르겠네요
He's lived here for years.
I don't know what you're talking about.
시침떼긴, 쟤 나가고
내가 이사 왔잖아
No, he moved out and I moved in.
Well, I think we'd remember
something like that.
누구나 뭔가를
잘못 기억할 수 있죠
나도 그럴 때 있어
I know I would.
좋은 지적이에요, 좋아요
That's a good point.
Okay, wow.
I guess I got the wrong apartment.
아무래도 제가 잘못 왔나 봐요
- 미안해요, 정말이에요
- 괜찮습니다
-I'm terribly sorry.
-Hey, no problem.
See you.
잘 가요
Goodbye, you fruit-drying psychopath.
잘 가라
과일 탈수시키는 사이코야
- 짐 푸는 거 도와 줄까?
- 아니, 됐어
-You want me to help you unpack?
-Nah, I'm okay.
한데 굳이 여기로 이사 올
필요는 없었어
Just so you know, I'm not
moving back in because I have to.
굳이 그럴 건 없었다는 거지
하지만 거긴...
I mean, I do have to, but....
It's just that that place,
it wasn't really....
내 말은 여기는...
I mean, this is....
집에 온 걸 축하해
Welcome home, man.
-A little foos?
-Absolutely!
- 게임할까?
- 물론이지
What happened to the foosball?
공이 왜 이래?
그건 멜론이야
It's a cantaloupe.
Are we gonna bring this out
every time Ross comes over?
로스가 올 때마다
개를 옮겨야 하는 거야?
로스가 돈을 많이 썼어
He paid a lot of money for it.
자세를 바꿀래
I'm gonna hold him a different way.
If you hated it so much,
why'd you buy it in the first place?
이렇게 싫은 걸 애초에
사긴 왜 사냐?
Well, I had a whole ceramic
zoo thing going over there.
거기선 동물들이 세트로 있어서
몰랐는데 여기선 되게 초라하다
But without the other ones,
it looks tacky.
훈련된 개야? 아님 화장실을
곳곳에 만들어 줘야 돼?
Is he housetrained or will he leave
little bathroom tiles all over?
Stay.
움직이지 마
가만있으라니까
Stay!
Good fake dog.
잘했다, 가짜 개야